Local 1199 Additional Files 5525
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Bloomfield Convalescent Home, 1968 (Box 63, Folder 4)
- Blue Hills Convalescent Home, 1968 (Box 63, Folder 5)
- Building Services Union - Conn., 1968-1969 (Box 63, Folder 6)
- Colchester Convalescent Home, 1969-1970 (Box 63, Folder 7)
- Community Health Service, 1970-1971 (Box 63, Folder 8)
- Connecticut Hospital - Organizing, 1968-1971 (Box 63, Folder 9)
- Danbury Pavilion, 1970-1971 (Box 63, Folder 10)
- Eden Park Nursing Home, 1969 (Box 63, Folder 11)
- Dr. Friedman's Convalescent Home, 1969 (Box 64, Folder 1)
- Golden Heights Manor Convalescent Home, 1968 (Box 64, Folder 2)
- Golden Manor Convalescent Home, 1968-1969 (Box 64, Folder 3)
- Hall-Brooke Hospital Foundation, 1967 (Box 64, Folder 4)
- Hamilton Pavilion, 1969 (Box 64, Folder 5)
- Hartford Convalescent Home, 1968-1971 (Box 64, Folder 6)
- Heritage Home - AMI, 1971 (Box 64, Folder 7)
- High Ridge Convalescent Home, 1969 (Box 64, Folder 8)
- Hughes Convalescent Home, 1968-1969 (Box 64, Folder 9)
- Manchester Memorial Hospital, 1971 (Box 65, Folder 1)
- Maple Lawn Hospital, 1968-1969 (Box 65, Folder 2)
- Meadowbrook Convalescent Home, 1971 (Box 65, Folder 3)
- New London, 1971 (Box 65, Folder 4)
- Park City Hospital, 1969 (Box 65, Folder 5)
- Pond Point Nursing Home, 1969-1969 (Box 65, Folder 6)
- Prospect Hospital, 1968-1971 (Box 65, Folder 7)
- Prospect Hospital, 1968-1971 (Box 65, Folder 8)
- Stephen E. Ronai, Negotiations - Pond Point, Stratford, and West Haven Manor (Box 65, Folder 9)
- Saint Mary Home, 1969-1970 (Box 65, Folder 10)
- Stula's Convalescent Hospital, 1970-1971 (Box 65, Folder 11)
- Westport Manor, 1968-1969 (Box 65, Folder 12)
- Bayonne Hospital, 1986 (Box 66, Folder 1)
- Chenny Nursing Home, 1986 (Box 66, Folder 2)
- Clover Rest Nursing Home, 1986 (Box 66, Folder 3)
- Community Hospital, 1986 (Box 66, Folder 4)
- Donnelly Hospital, 1986-1969 (Box 66, Folder 5)
- Foothill Acres Nursing Home, 1970 (Box 66, Folder 6)
- Hillcrest Nursing Home, 1971 (Box 66, Folder 7)
- Lawrencirulla Nursing Home, 1971-1972 (Box 66, Folder 8)
- Medi-Center of America, 1971 (Box 66, Folder 9)
- Memorial Center for Women, 1968 (Box 66, Folder 10)
- Middlesex General Hospital, 1970 (Box 66, Folder 11)
- Mills Nursing Home, 1968 (Box 66, Folder 12)
- Mountainside Hospital, 1964-1966 (Box 66, Folder 13)
- New Jersey General, 1958-1970 (Box 67, Folder 1)
- New Jersey General, 1958-1970 (Box 67, Folder 2)
- New Jersey Pharmacists, 1974-1975 (Box 67, Folder 3)
- Newark Hospital, 1968 (Box 67, Folder 4)
- Presbyterian Hospital, 1964-1965 (Box 67, Folder 5)
- North Carolina (News Clippings), 1969-1970 (Box 68, Folder 1)
- Aaron Convalescent Home, 1971 (Box 69, Folder 1)
- Alaska Nursing Home, 1971 (Box 69, Folder 2)
- Case Western Reserve University, 1970-1971 (Box 69, Folder 3)
- Cincinnati Convalescent, 1971 (Box 69, Folder 4)
- Franklin Nursing Home, 1970 (Box 69, Folder 5)
- Methodist Home on College Hill, 1971 (Box 69, Folder 6)
- Saga Food Service, 1970-1971 (Box 69, Folder 7)
- Stillhaven Nursing Home, 1970-1971 (Box 69, Folder 8)
- Vernon Convalescent Home, 1971-1974 (Box 69, Folder 9)
- Victory Park Nursing Home, 1972 (Box 69, Folder 10)
- Villa Hope Nursing Home, 1971-1973 (Box 69, Folder 11)
- Bishop Nursing Home, 1970 (Box 70, Folder 1)
- Boulevard Nursing Home, 1969 (Box 70, Folder 2)
- Carnegie Institute, 1970-1971 (Box 70, Folder 3)
- IBUE Service Unit - Temple University, 1972 (Box 70, Folder 4)
- Interstate Blood Bank, Inc., 1969 (Box 70, Folder 5)
- Montfiore Hospital, 1970-1972 (Box 70, Folder 6)
- Rest Haven Nursing Home, 1970-1971 (Box 70, Folder 7)
- Rosemont Manor Nursing Home, 1972 (Box 70, Folder 8)
- St. Agnes Hospital, 1970 (Box 70, Folder 9)
- Sarah Allen Nursing Home, 1969 (Box 70, Folder 10)
- Stenton Hall Nursing Home, 1971 (Box 70, Folder 11)
- Stetson Hospital, 1971 (Box 70, Folder 12)
- William Pepper Laboratory, 1972 (Box 70, Folder 13)
- Pennsylvania - General, 1970-1972 (Box 71, Folder 1)
- Harrisburg - 1199C, 1969-1972 (Box 71, Folder 2)
- Philadelphia - 1199C General, 1970-1972 (Box 71, Folder 3)
- Philadelphia - 1199C Office General, 1970-1972 (Box 71, Folder 4)
- Philadelphia - 1199C Legal, 1969-1971 (Box 71, Folder 5)
- Philadelphia - 1199C Releases, 1971 (Box 71, Folder 6)
- Dues Information, 1971 (Box 72, Folder 1)
- Legal, 1971 (Box 72, Folder 2)
- Office - General, 1970-1972 (Box 72, Folder 3)
- Wilkes-Barre Local 1199P, 1970-1972 (Box 72, Folder 4)
- Allentown Hospital Association, 1971-1972 (Box 72, Folder 5)
- Black, F. W. Community Hospital, 1970-1972 (Box 72, Folder 6)
- Boise Cascade Urban Development Corporation, 1972 (Box 72, Folder 7)
- Bucks County Hospital, 1966 (Box 72, Folder 8)
- Carnegie Institute - Library, 1970-1972 (Box 72, Folder 9)
- Citizens General Hospital, 1971-1972 (Box 72, Folder 10)
- Conemaugh Valley Memorial Hospital, 1971-1972 (Box 72, Folder 11)
- Erie Osteopathic Hospital, 1971-1972 (Box 72, Folder 12)
- Forbes Parulian Pittsburgh, 1970-1972 (Box 72, Folder 13)
- Famot Hospital, 1971-1972 (Box 72, Folder 14)
- H.C.S.C. Laundry, 1971-1972 (Box 72, Folder 15)
- Hospital Central Services, Inc., 1971-1972 (Box 72, Folder 16)
- Jewish Home of Eastern Pa., 1971-1972 (Box 73, Folder 1)
- Laurel Hill Nursing Home, 1971 (Box 73, Folder 2)
- McGinley Maintenance Co., 1970-1971 (Box 73, Folder 3)
- Masonic Home of Pennsylvania, 1971 (Box 73, Folder 4)
- Mercy Hospital - Wilkes-Barre, 1970-1972 (Box 73, Folder 5)
- Mercy Hospital - Wilkes-Barre, 1970-1972 (Box 73, Folder 6)
- Mercy Hospital - Wilkes-Barre, 1970-1972 (Box 73, Folder 7)
- Penn Building Maintenance Co., 1971-1972 (Box 73, Folder 8)
- Presbyterian University Hospital, 1969-1971 (Box 73, Folder 9)
- Reading Community General Hospital, 1971-1972 (Box 73, Folder 10)
- Rochester General Hospital, 1972 (Box 73, Folder 11)
- St. Margaret's Hospital, 1969 (Box 73, Folder 12)
- Suburban General Hospital, 1972 (Box 73, Folder 13)
- Uniontown Hospital, 1970 (Box 73, Folder 14)
- Windber Hospital, 1971 (Box 73, Folder 15)
- Rhode Island - General, 1970-1972 (Box 74, Folder 1)
- Rhode Island - General, 1970-1972 (Box 74, Folder 2)
- Cramston General Hospital, 1972 (Box 74, Folder 3)
- Nelson Nursing Home, 1970-1971 (Box 74, Folder 4)
- Pawtucket Memorial Hospital, 1972 (Box 74, Folder 5)
- Charleston, S.C. - 1199B, 1969-1972 (Box 75, Folder 1)
- Charleston, S.C. - 1199B, 1969-1972 (Box 75, Folder 2)
- Charleston, S.C. - 1199B, 1969-1972 (Box 75, Folder 3)
- Columbia, 1970-1972 (Box 75, Folder 4)
- Charleston - Dues information (Box 75, Folder 5)
- C. M. Tucker Human Resources Center, 1972 (Box 75, Folder 6)
- West Virginia - General, 1970-1972 (Box 76, Folder 1)
- Guyan Valley Hospital, 1970-1971 (Box 76, Folder 2)
- Logan General Hospital, 1970 (Box 76, Folder 3)
- Madison General Hospital, 1970 (Box 76, Folder 4)
- Oak Hill Hospital, 1970-1971 (Box 76, Folder 5)
- Richlands Center Hospital, 1972 (Box 76, Folder 6)
- Stevens Clinic Hospital, 1970-1972 (Box 76, Folder 7)
- Arizona General, 1972 (Box 77, Folder 1)
- Canadian Union Material, 1968-1970 (Box 77, Folder 2)
- Florida - Organization, 1968-1972 (Box 77, Folder 3)
- Florida - New Fern Restorium, 1968 (Box 77, Folder 4)
- Florida - NOC Office, 1968-1969 (Box 77, Folder 5)
- St. Petersburg, 1968 (Box 77, Folder 6)
- Atlanta, Georgia, 1968-1969 (Box 77, Folder 7)
- Illinois- Chicago, 1967-1971 (Box 77, Folder 8)
- Kansas - General, 1968 (Box 77, Folder 9)
- Louisville, Kentucky, 1970-1971 (Box 77, Folder 10)
- New Jersey Organizing Team Meetings, 1964 (Box 77, Folder 11)
- N.Y.S. Correspondence, Miscellaneous Organizations, 1965-1969 (Box 77, Folder 12)
- N.Y.S. National Organization - General, 1967-1970 (Box 77, Folder 13)
- N.Y.S. Organization - General, 1963-1970 (Box 77, Folder 14)
- N.Y.S. Organizing Team Meetings, 1964-1966 (Box 77, Folder 15)
- Puerto Rico, 1970 (Box 77, Folder 16)
- Tennessee, 1969 (Box 77, Folder 17)
- Bel Air Nursing Home, 1973-1974 (Box 78, Folder 1)
- Birchwood Nursing Home, 1971-1974 (Box 78, Folder 2)
- Booth Memorial Hospital, 1971-1974 (Box 78, Folder 3)
- Booth Memorial Hospital, 1971-1974 (Box 78, Folder 4)
- Brookhaven Memorial Hospital, 1974 (Box 78, Folder 5)
- Convalescent Home of N.Y. Guild, 1969-1973 (Box 78, Folder 6)
- Eastern Long Island Hospital, 1968-1974 (Box 78, Folder 7)
- Eastern Long Island Hospital Service and Maintenance, 1973-1974 (Box 78, Folder 8)
- Flushing Medical Center, 1968-1974 (Box 79, Folder 1)
- Forest Manor Health Related Facility, 1972-1974 (Box 79, Folder 2)
- Freeport Hospital, 1969-1974 (Box 79, Folder 3)
- Grace Plaza Home of Great Neck, 1972-1974 (Box 79, Folder 4)
- Hempstead General Hospital, 1971-1974 (Box 79, Folder 5)
- Hilaire Farm Nursing Home, 1971-1974 (Box 79, Folder 6)
- Hillside Hospital, 1971-1974 (Box 79, Folder 7)
- Jewish Institute of Geriatric Care, 1970-1974 (Box 79, Folder 8)
- Little Flower Nursing Home, 1973-1974 (Box 80, Folder 1)
- Long Island Jewish Hospital, 1973-1974 (Box 80, Folder 2)
- Long Island Jewish Hospital, 1973-1974 (Box 80, Folder 3)
- Manhasset Medical Center Hospital, 1971-1974 (Box 80, Folder 4)
- Montclair Nursing Home, 1972-1974 (Box 80, Folder 5)
- Patchoque Nursing Home, 1974 (Box 80, Folder 6)
- Peninsula Hospital Center, 1973-1974 (Box 80, Folder 7)
- Ross Nursing Home, 1968-1974 (Box 80, Folder 8)
- St. John's-Queens Hospital, 1971-1975 (Box 80, Folder 9)
- Sayville Nursing Home, 1970-1974 (Box 81, Folder 1)
- Seagrit Village of Old Israel, 1971-1974 (Box 81, Folder 2)
- Smithtown Nursing Home, 1972-1973 (Box 81, Folder 3)
- South Oaks Psychiatric Hospital, 1973-1974 (Box 81, Folder 4)
- South Oaks Psychiatric Hospital, 1973-1974 (Box 81, Folder 5)
- South Shore Hospital, 1973-1974 (Box 81, Folder 6)
- Southampton Hospital, 1973-1974 (Box 81, Folder 7)
- Southside Hospital, 1969-1974 (Box 81, Folder 8)
- Southside Hospital, 1969-1974 (Box 81, Folder 9)
- Southside Hospital, 1969-1974 (Box 81, Folder 10)
- Sunrise Manor Nursing Home, 1973-1974 (Box 82, Folder 1)
- Syosset Hospital, 1970-1974 (Box 82, Folder 2)
- Syosset Hospital, 1970-1974 (Box 82, Folder 3)
- Todd Nursing Home, 1970-1974 (Box 82, Folder 4)
- Woodbury Nursing Home, 1973-1974 (Box 82, Folder 5)
- United Presbyterian Residence, 1972-1974 (Box 82, Folder 6)
- United Presbyterian Residence, 1972-1974 (Box 82, Folder 7)
- Westhampton Nursing Home, 1972-1974 (Box 82, Folder 8)
- Adelphi Hospital, 1969 (Box 83, Folder 1)
- Amalgamated 298 (Union City), 1955-1968 (Box 83, Folder 2)
- Bayshore Nursing Home, 1964 (Box 83, Folder 3)
- Berkshire Nursing Center (Box 83, Folder 4)
- Beth Israel Medical Center, 1970 (Box 83, Folder 5)
- Blythedale Children's Hospital, 1968 (Box 83, Folder 6)
- Brandywine Nursing Home, 1965 (Box 83, Folder 7)
- Briarcliff Nursing Home, 1966 (Box 83, Folder 8)
- Brooklyn Hebrew Home, 1963 (Box 83, Folder 9)
- Central General Hospital, 1964 (Box 84, Folder 1)
- Davies Nursing Home, 1964-1966 (Box 84, Folder 2)
- Dr. Castraviejo Hospital, 1966-1970 (Box 84, Folder 3)
- Ferncliff Manor Nursing Home, 1965 (Box 84, Folder 4)
- Fountain Medical Group, 1970 (Box 84, Folder 5)
- Frances Scherrier, 1966 (Box 84, Folder 6)
- Franklin General Hospital, 1964 (Box 84, Folder 7)
- Florence Nightingale Nursing Home, 1968 (Box 84, Folder 8)
- Graham Nursing Home, 1969-1970 (Box 84, Folder 9)
- Holley Patterson Home (Box 84, Folder 10)
- Huntington Hospital (Box 84, Folder 11)
- Lawrence Hospital, 1965 (Box 84, Folder 12)
- Lawrence Hospital, 1965 (Box 84, Folder 13)
- Long Beach Hospital, 1965 (Box 85, Folder 1)
- Long Island Nursing Home, 1970 (Box 85, Folder 2)
- Mayfair Rest Home, 1964 (Box 85, Folder 3)
- Menorah Home and Hospital for Aged (Box 85, Folder 4)
- Mercer Hospital, 1965 (Box 85, Folder 5)
- Methodist Hospital of Brooklyn, 1968 (Box 85, Folder 6)
- Mid-Island Hospital, 1967 (Box 85, Folder 7)
- Miller's Center, 1966-1968 (Box 85, Folder 8)
- New York Cardiac Center, 1965 (Box 85, Folder 9)
- New York General, 1962-1970 (Box 85, Folder 10)
- New York General, 1962-1970 (Box 85, Folder 11)
- Noah Nursing Home, 1964 (Box 86, Folder 1)
- Overlook Hospital, 1963-1967 (Box 86, Folder 2)
- Phelps Memorial Hospital, 1974 (Box 86, Folder 3)
- Polyclinic Hospital, 1968 (Box 86, Folder 4)
- Prospect Heights, 1969 (Box 86, Folder 5)
- Rockefeller Institute, 1967-1969 (Box 86, Folder 6)
- Rockville Center, 1970 (Box 86, Folder 7)
- Rofay Nursing Home, 1966 (Box 86, Folder 8)
- Sarah Lawrence (Box 86, Folder 9)
- St. Elizabeth Hospital, 1968 (Box 86, Folder 10)
- St. Mary's Hospital (Amsterdam), 1970 (Box 86, Folder 11)
- St. Mary's Hospital (Brooklyn), 1971 (Box 86, Folder 12)
- St. Patrick's Home for Aged, 1964-1965 (Box 86, Folder 13)
- Samaritan Hospital, 1966 (Box 86, Folder 14)
- Sands Point Nursing Home, 1965 (Box 86, Folder 15)
- SanSouci Nursing Home, 1964 (Box 86, Folder 16)
- Shore Memorial Hospital, 1965-1966 (Box 86, Folder 17)
- Smithtown General Hospital, 1964 (Box 86, Folder 18)
- White Plains Hospital, 1967-1971 (Box 86, Folder 19)
- Yonkers General Hospital (Box 86, Folder 20)
- Yonkers Hamilton Sanitorium, Inc., 1969 (Box 86, Folder 21)
- Yonkers Professional Hospital, 1968-1969 (Box 86, Folder 22)
- Adams House Hospital (Box 87, Folder 1)
- Adelphi Hospital (Box 87, Folder 2)
- Aliquippi Hospital (Box 87, Folder 3)
- Alleghany General Hospital (Box 87, Folder 4)
- AMI Enfield Nursing Home (Box 87, Folder 5)
- Ashton Hall Hospital (Box 87, Folder 6)
- Association Home (Box 87, Folder 7)
- Josephine Baird Home (Box 87, Folder 8)
- Baltimore Leaflets (Box 87, Folder 9)
- Baltimore Printed (Box 87, Folder 10)
- Bayonne Hospital (Box 87, Folder 11)
- Beechknoll Convalescent Center (Box 87, Folder 12)
- Berkshire Medical Center (Box 87, Folder 13)
- Blue Hills Convalescent Home (Box 87, Folder 14)
- Booth Memorial Hospital (Box 87, Folder 15)
- Boulevard Nursing Home (Box 87, Folder 16)
- Broad Street Hospital (Box 87, Folder 17)
- Brookhaven Memorial Hospital (Box 87, Folder 18)
- Bryn Mawr Hospital (Box 87, Folder 19)
- Buckley Nursing Home (Box 87, Folder 20)
- Case Western Reserve University (Box 87, Folder 21)
- Catholic Hospital General (Box 87, Folder 22)
- Central Suffolk Hospital (Box 87, Folder 23)
- Charleston 1199B (Box 87, Folder 24)
- Children's Hospital (Philadelphia) (Box 87, Folder 25)
- Children's Hospital (Washington) (Box 87, Folder 26)
- Citizens General Hospital (Box 87, Folder 27)
- Colchester Convalescent Home (Box 87, Folder 28)
- Columbia Hospital (Pittsburgh) (Box 87, Folder 29)
- Community General Hospital (Box 87, Folder 30)
- Connecticut General (Box 87, Folder 31)
- County Hospital (Charleston, S.C.) (Box 87, Folder 32)
- Cranston General Hospital (R.I.) (Box 87, Folder 33)
- Crown Nursing Home (Box 87, Folder 34)
- Danbury Pavilion (Box 88, Folder 1)
- Dayton, Ohio - General (Box 88, Folder 2)
- Detroit Leaflets (Box 88, Folder 3)
- Donnelly Hospital (Box 88, Folder 4)
- Duke University Medical Center (Box 88, Folder 5)
- Dumont Nursing Home (Box 88, Folder 6)
- Durham (Box 88, Folder 7)
- Eastern Long Island Hospital (Box 88, Folder 8)
- Einstein North (Philadelphia) (Box 88, Folder 9)
- Einstein South (Philadelphia) (Box 88, Folder 10)
- Englewood Hospital (Box 88, Folder 11)
- Foothill (Box 88, Folder 12)
- Friedman Nursing Home (Box 88, Folder 13)
- Geri-Care (Springfield, Mass.) (Box 88, Folder 14)
- Golden Manor Nursing Home (Box 88, Folder 15)
- Hahneman Hospital (Box 88, Folder 16)
- Hartford General Hospital (Box 88, Folder 17)
- Hamilton Pavilion (Box 88, Folder 18)
- Harrisburg Hospital (Box 88, Folder 19)
- Hartford General Hospital (Box 88, Folder 20)
- Hawkins Nursing Home (Box 88, Folder 21)
- Hempstead Hospital (Box 88, Folder 22)
- Heritage House (Box 88, Folder 23)
- High Ridge Convalescent Home (Box 88, Folder 24)
- Hillside Hospital (Box 88, Folder 25)
- Home for Old Men and Aged Couples (Box 88, Folder 26)
- Home for the Sages of Israel (Box 88, Folder 27)
- Hospital University of Pennsylvania (Box 88, Folder 28)
- Hughes Convalescent Home (Box 88, Folder 29)
- Inglis House (Box 89, Folder 1)
- Interstate Blood Bank, Inc. (Box 89, Folder 2)
- Jefferson Hospital (Box 89, Folder 3)
- Jefferson, T. Hospital (Box 89, Folder 4)
- Jewish Home for the Aged (Conn.) (Box 89, Folder 5)
- Jewish Home for the Aged (R.I.) (Box 89, Folder 6)
- Jewish Home and Hospital for Aged (Pittsburgh) (Box 89, Folder 7)
- Jewish Home of Scranton (Box 89, Folder 8)
- Lawrence Memorial (Box 89, Folder 9)
- Lawrenceville Nursing Home (Box 89, Folder 10)
- Leaflets - General National Organizing Committee (Box 89, Folder 11)
- Lewistown Hospital (Pa.) (Box 89, Folder 12)
- Longhill Convalescent Home (Conn.) (Box 89, Folder 13)
- Long Island College (Box 89, Folder 14)
- Long Island Nursing Home (Box 89, Folder 15)
- Lutheran Home (Box 89, Folder 16)
- Lutheran Hospital (Box 89, Folder 17)
- Lying In Hospital (Box 89, Folder 18)
- Mapleview Hospital (Box 89, Folder 19)
- Mary Manning Walsh Home (Box 89, Folder 20)
- McKeesport Hospital (Box 89, Folder 21)
- Meadowbrook Convalescent Hospital (Box 89, Folder 22)
- Medical College (S.C.) (Box 89, Folder 23)
- Mercy Hospital (Philadelphia) (Box 89, Folder 24)
- Mercy Hospital (Pittsburgh) (Box 89, Folder 25)
- Mercy Hospital (Wilkes-Barre) (Box 89, Folder 26)
- Methodist Church Home (Box 89, Folder 27)
- Metropolitan Hospital (Box 89, Folder 28)
- Miami Valley Hospital (Box 89, Folder 29)
- Middlesex Hospital (Box 89, Folder 30)
- Milford Heights (Box 89, Folder 31)
- Montfiore Hospital (Box 89, Folder 32)
- Morris Cafritz Hospital (Box 89, Folder 33)
- Mt. Sinai Hospital (Box 89, Folder 34)
- Mt. Sinai Hospital (Box 89, Folder 35)
- Mt. Vernon Hospital (Box 89, Folder 36)
- National Union Leaflets (Box 90, Folder 1)
- NOC Forms (Box 90, Folder 2)
- New Haven Convalescent Home (Box 90, Folder 3)
- Newport Hospital (Box 90, Folder 4)
- Newark Beth Israel Hospital (Box 90, Folder 5)
- Northern Westchester Hospital (Box 90, Folder 6)
- Norwalk Hospital (Box 90, Folder 7)
- Norwichtown (Box 90, Folder 8)
- Ohio (General) (Box 90, Folder 9)
- Park Crescent Home (Box 90, Folder 10)
- Parkview Nursing Home (Box 90, Folder 11)
- Pennsylvania Hospital (Box 90, Folder 12)
- Philadelphia General Leaflets (Box 90, Folder 13)
- Philadelphia Geriatrics Center (Box 90, Folder 14)
- Pittsburgh General (Box 90, Folder 15)
- Polyclinic Hospital (Box 90, Folder 16)
- Pottstown Hospital (Box 90, Folder 17)
- Presbyterian University Hospital (Box 91, Folder 1)
- Prospect Gardens (Box 91, Folder 2)
- Providence Health Centers (Box 91, Folder 3)
- Rest Haven Convalescent Home (Box 91, Folder 4)
- Sarah Allen Nursing Home (Box 91, Folder 5)
- St. Agnes Hospital (Box 91, Folder 6)
- St. Francis Hospital (Box 91, Folder 7)
- St. Margaret's Hospital (Box 91, Folder 8)
- St. Mary's Home (Box 91, Folder 9)
- St. Mary's Hospital (Conn.) (Box 91, Folder 10)
- St. Mary's Hospital (N.J.) (Box 91, Folder 11)
- St. Mary's Hospital (Pa.) (Box 91, Folder 12)
- Southside Hospital (Box 91, Folder 13)
- Springfield Hospital Medical Center (Box 91, Folder 14)
- Stony Brook College (Box 91, Folder 15)
- Stratford Hospital (Box 91, Folder 16)
- Stula's Convalescent Hospital (Box 91, Folder 17)
- Temples Hospital (Box 91, Folder 18)
- Tri-County Hospital (Box 91, Folder 19)
- Uniontown Hospital (Box 91, Folder 20)
- Uptown Hospital (Box 91, Folder 21)
- Villa Hope Nursing Home (Box 91, Folder 22)
- Washington Hospital Center (Box 91, Folder 23)
- White Plains Hospital (Box 91, Folder 24)
- Workmen's Circle Home (Box 91, Folder 25)
- Yonkers General Hospital (Box 91, Folder 26)
- Yonkers Professional Hospital (Box 91, Folder 27)
- Miscellaneous Leaflet File (Box 91, Folder 28)
- Administrative Health Programs, 1971 (Box 92, Folder 1)
- Attendance, Programs, Assignments, Guests, 1972 (Box 92, Folder 2)
- Clairborne Pell Bill, 1970-1971 (Box 92, Folder 3)
- Community Council, 1971-1974 (Box 92, Folder 4)
- Community Council, 1971-1974 (Box 92, Folder 5)
- Health Care Conference III (June 2) Correspondence, Memos, 1973 (Box 92, Folder 6)
- Health Care Conference III Material for Report, 1973 (Box 92, Folder 7)
- Health Care Conference III Material for Report, 1973 (Box 92, Folder 8)
- Laboratory - Meetings, Minutes, Attendance, 1972-1974 (Box 93, Folder 1)
- Memos and Correspondence, 1971 (Box 93, Folder 2)
- Miscellaneous, 1971-1972 (Box 93, Folder 3)
- National Health Insurance Act Dingell (H.R. 48), 1971 (Box 93, Folder 4)
- National Health Insurance - Medicredit, 1970-1971 (Box 93, Folder 5)
- Nixon Bills, 1971 (Box 93, Folder 6)
- Planning, 1966 (Box 93, Folder 7)
- Policy Statement - Attendance, Panel Leaders, Press, 1971 (Box 93, Folder 8)
- Professional Conference, 1973-1974 (Box 93, Folder 9)
- Speakers - Holloman Presentation, 1971 (Box 93, Folder 10)
- Work Shop Materials, 1972 (Box 93, Folder 11)
- Health Services Distribution, 1970-1972 (Box 94, Folder 1)
- Nassau-Suffolk Regional Medical Program, 1969-1970 (Box 94, Folder 2)
- Physician Assistant, 1968-1971 (Box 94, Folder 3)
- Physician Assistant, 1968-1971 (Box 94, Folder 4)
- Physician Assistant, 1968-1971 (Box 94, Folder 5)
- Physician Assistant, 1968-1971 (Box 94, Folder 6)
- Regional Advisory Group - Agendas, 1973-1974 (Box 95, Folder 1)
- Washington Report on Medicine and Health, 1971-1972 (Box 96, Folder 1)
- Washington Report on Medicine and Health, 1971-1972 (Box 96, Folder 2)
- AMA and AHA Weeklys, 1972-1973 (Box 96, Folder 3)
- Negotiations Committee Minutes (Box 97, Folder 1)
- X-Ray Committee (Box 97, Folder 2)
- Training and Upgrading Fund (Box 97, Folder 3)
- Training and Upgrading Fund (Box 97, Folder 4)
- Guild Delegate Committee (Box 97, Folder 5)
- Adelphi Hospital (Box 98, Folder 1)
- Adelphi Hospital (Box 98, Folder 2)
- Adelphi Hospital (Box 98, Folder 3)
- Adelphi Hospital (Box 98, Folder 4)
- Adelphi Hospital (Box 98, Folder 5)
- American Medical Insurance (Box 98, Folder 6)
- Animal Medical Center (Box 98, Folder 7)
- Beekman Hospital (Box 98, Folder 8)
- Blueberry Inc. (Box 98, Folder 9)
- Brooklyn Hospital (Box 98, Folder 10)
- Caledonian Hospital (Box 98, Folder 11)
- Center for Reproductive and Sexual Health (Box 98, Folder 12)
- Center for Reproductive and Sexual Health (Box 98, Folder 13)
- Center for Reproductive and Sexual Health (Box 98, Folder 14)
- Evangelical Home for the Aged (Box 99, Folder 1)
- Evangelical Home for the Aged (Box 99, Folder 2)
- Franklin General Hospital (Box 99, Folder 3)
- Hillside Hospital (Box 99, Folder 4)
- James Weldon Johnson Community Centers, Inc. (Box 99, Folder 5)
- Lenox Hill Hospital (Box 99, Folder 6)
- Long Island College Hospital (Box 99, Folder 7)
- Margaret Sanger Research Bureau, Inc. (Box 99, Folder 8)
- Margaret Sanger Research Bureau, Inc. (Box 99, Folder 9)
- Margaret Sanger Research Bureau, Inc. (Box 99, Folder 10)
- New Rochelle Hospital (Box 100, Folder 1)
- New York Eye and Ear Infirmary (Box 100, Folder 2)
- New York Foundling Hospital (Box 100, Folder 3)
- Nyack Hospital (Box 100, Folder 4)
- Planned Parenthood (Box 100, Folder 5)
- Putnam Community Hospital (Box 100, Folder 6)
- Rockefeller University (Box 100, Folder 7)
- St. Barnabas (N.J.) (Box 100, Folder 8)
- St. Joseph's (N.J.) (Box 100, Folder 9)
- St. Luke's (Newburgh) (Box 100, Folder 10)
- St. Vincent's Hospital (Box 100, Folder 11)
- St. Vincent's Hospital (Staten Island) (Box 100, Folder 12)
- St. Vincent's Hospital (Box 100, Folder 13)
- St. Vincent's Hospital (Box 100, Folder 14)
- South Nassau Community Hospital (Box 100, Folder 15)
- South Oaks Hospital (Box 100, Folder 16)
- Speedwell Services for Children (Box 100, Folder 17)
- Strong Memorial Hospital (Box 100, Folder 18)
- Sunrise Hospital (Box 100, Folder 19)
- Swedish Hospital (Box 100, Folder 20)
- Teachers College (Box 100, Folder 21)
- Valley Hospital (Box 100, Folder 22)
- Washington Heights (Box 100, Folder 23)